Oh,look, Saturn 3is on.
看啊 正在放"土星三号"呢
I don't want to watch Saturn
3. Deep Space Nine is better.
我不想看"土星三号" "深空九号"更好看
How isDeep Space
Ninebetter thanSaturn 3?
"深空九号"哪有"土星三号"好看
Simple subtraction will
tell you it's six better.
简单的减法告诉你 好看六个数儿
Compromise. WatchBabylon 5.
折衷一下 看"巴比伦五号"好了
In what sense is that a compromise?
这是哪门子折衷啊?
Well,five is partway between three...
恩 五处在三和九之间...
Never mind.
算了
I'll tell you what. How about
we go rock-paper-scissors?
要不这样 我们来用石头剪子布决定
Ooh,I don't think so.
不行 我不干
Anecdotal evidence suggests that
in the game of rock-paper-scissors,
数据统计显示 在石头-剪子-布中
players familiar with each other will tie 75 to 80%
of the time due to the limited number of outcomes.
由于出法太少 相熟的玩家
有75%到80%的可能性会打平
I suggest rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock.
我建议采用石头-剪刀-布-蜥蜴-史波克
What?
什么
It's very simple.
很简单
Scissors cuts paper.
剪子剪布
Paper covers rock.
布包石头
Rock crushes lizard.
石头压蜥蜴
Lizard poisons Spock.
蜥蜴毒死史波克
Spock smashes scissors.
史波克轰碎剪子
Scissors decapitates lizard.
剪子腰斩蜥蜴
Lizard eats paper.
蜥蜴吃布
Paper disproves Spock.
布否定史波克
Spock vaporizes rock.
史波克蒸发石头
And as it always has,
rock crushes scissors.
再加上一如既往的规则 石头砸剪子
Okay,I think I got it.
行啊 我应该会玩了
Rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock!
石头-剪刀-布-蜥蜴-史波克
Hello,boys.
嗨 伙计们
Ahoy,matey.
啊嗬 朋友
Noticed the eye patch,did you?
看见这个眼罩了 对吧
It's all part of a technique I've
been studying for picking up women.
这是我泡妞宝典中的一种技巧
You employ a visual display designed to
make yourself distinctive and memorable.
给别人视觉上的冲击力
让你显的与众不同
Oh,yes,like the male peacock with brilliant plumage
or the rutting baboon with engorged hindquarters.
就像雄孔雀有漂亮的羽毛
或者发情的狒狒有隆起的臀部一样
Or in this case,the bar
mitzvah boy with pinkeye.
或者可以这么说
像一个得红眼病的犹太男
Mock me if you will, but it works.
尽管嘲笑我吧 不过这招确实有用
You show up at a club in something distinctive,
scope out your target and toss out some negs.
你穿成这样去泡吧
寻找你的目标 然后抛出几句"反话"
What are negs?
啥叫"反话"?
A neg is a negative compliment that
throws a pretty woman off her game,
就是反向的恭维
让漂亮女性忘了她们的小缺陷
like "Normally,I'm not turned on
by big teeth, but on you,they work."
好比这样 "通常情况 牙有些大的女士
不会让我动心 但你就不一样了"
I got a whole list of 'em.
Who wants to be my wingman?
我有一大堆招数呢
谁想做我的泡妞搭档
You're not gonna need a wingman.
你用不着找个泡妞搭档
You're gonna need a paramedic.
你应该找个护理搭档
Howard,your scooter's blocking my car.
Howard 你的摩托挡住我的车了
Aw,did you get pinkeye again?
喔 你又得红眼病了?
Step one: she notices the eye patch.
第一步 她注意到了我的眼罩
May I say,Penny, not a lot of women could
look as hot as you do with such greasy hair?
这么说吧 Penny 不是所有女人
都和你一样 头发油油的还这么性感
Yeah,just move your stupid scooter before
I pick it up and throw it in the dumpster.
赶紧把你那破摩托车开走
不然我马上扔进垃圾堆
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 八重樱 王泳东 opp
校对: 欧屁屁
时间轴: 咔肉肉
双语:徐小帆
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode08
天才理论传
第二季 第8集
I'm sorry,but I'm not going to watchThe Clone
WarsTV series until I've seen The Clone Warsmovie.
对不起 我现在不看克隆人战争的电视剧
我得先看电影版
I prefer to let George Lucas
disappoint me in the order he intended.
乔治卢卡斯肯定会让我失望
就顺着他的顺序来吧
Well,I want to watch it now.
我现在就要看
Then I believe we've arrived at another quintessential
rock-paper-scissors- lizard-Spock moment.
那又到了石头-剪子-布-蜥蜴-史波克
的经典一刻了
Watch whatever you want.
你爱看什么看什么吧
I saw what you did there.
我看到你的魄力了
What'd I do?
我的魄力?
Hello. Hey,Howard. What's wrong?
嗨 Howard 什么事
Okay. Okay, we'll be right there.
好 好 我们这就过去
What happened?
发生什么事了
Howard's at the Mars Rover
lab. He says he's in trouble.
Howard在火星探测器实验室
他说遇到麻烦了
- Defcon 5.
- Defcon 5?
- 五级战备状态
- 五级战备状态?
Well,there's no need to rush.
这么说用不着急着赶过去
What?
什么?
Defcon 5 means "no danger."
五级战备状态意味着"没有危险"
Defcon 1 is a cris.
一级战备状态才是危机来临
How can 5 not be worse than 1?
五级怎么会还不如一级?
Yeah,Star Trek V worse thanI.
就是啊  星际迷航第五部比第一部难看
Okay,first of all, that's a
comparison of quality, not intensity.
首先来说 我们比较的是影片的品质
而不是激烈程度
Secondly,Star Trek I is
orders-of-magnitude worse thanStar Trek V.
再说 星战迷航第一部差第五部
不止一个数量级
Are you joking?
你开什么玩笑
Star Trek Vis the standard against
which all badness is measured.
星际迷航5简直就是
"没有最烂只有更烂"的最好诠释
No,no.
不对 不对
Star Trek V has specific
failures in writing and direction,
星际迷航5只是剧本失败 导演很烂
whileStar Trek Ifails across the board: art
direction,costuming, music,sound editing.
但星际迷航1 所有部分都很烂
艺术执导 服装 配乐 音效剪辑
Can we just forget I said Defcon and go?
表再纠结战备状态了 赶快走吧
Star Trek V.
星际迷航5
All right,will you at least stipulate thatStar
Trek IV: The Voyage Homeis inarguably the best?
至少你得承认 "星际迷航4:重回地球"
是最好看的 这毫无争议
I have three words
for you: Wrath of Khan.
送你五个字 凯恩的愤怒 (星际迷航2)
- Oh,thank God, you're here.
- What's the emergency?
- 感谢上帝 你们可来了
- 什么事这么急
I got the Mars Rover stuck in a ditch.
我把火星探测器卡在一条裂沟里了
Where?
在哪里?
On a dusty highway just
outside Bakersfield.
Bekersfield郊外
一条脏兮兮的高速公路上
Where do you think? On Mars!
还能在哪儿啊?! 火星呗!
Howard, is everything okay?
Howard 没事吧?
Yeah,baby,I'll be right in.
当然 宝贝 我就来
You brought a girl to the
Mars Rover control room?
你还把姑娘带进了火星探测器控制室?
Yeah,I picked her up in
the bar. She's a doctor.
是啊 我在酒吧搭上她的 她是个医生
One free barium enema, and my
mother won't care she's not Jewish.
送一次免费的钡餐灌肠
我妈肯定再不介意她不是犹太人了
Wait a minute. So the eye
patch and the insults worked?
等一下 这么说眼罩和反向恭维奏效了
No,there were three other
guys with eye patches.
没有 那里还有三个带眼罩的
It was a fiasco.
简直一败涂地
What did work was, "How'd you like to
visit a secret government facility?"
奏效的是这招:
"你想不想参观一处秘密政府设施?"
So what exactly do you want us to do?
那你到底要我们做些什么?
I need you and Raj to help me
get the Rover out of the ditch
我要你和Raj
帮我把火星探测器从沟里拖出来
and I need you to get Stephanie out
before somebody notices she's here.
你呢 在别人发现之前
把Stephanie从这带走
She doesn't exactly have clearance.
她进来都没开证明
Really? They don't let
strange women from honky-tonks
真的吗? 这儿不许泡廉价酒馆的女人进来
come in and play with $200 million
government projects on distant planets?
拿遥远星球上价值2亿的政府装备
当玩具玩?
Yes,I was bad.
好吧 我错了
Maybe she'll spank me.
也许她会给我一巴掌
Can we please move on?
开始行动了好吧?
Hey,Howard,you know, it's getting late,
so do I get to drive this thing or what?
嗨 Howard 时间不早了
我能开始操纵这玩意儿了吗?
Yeah. No. I'm sorry,
but something's come up.
不好意思 出了点状况
Kind of a Mars Rover...
火星探测器...
Mars Rover can Howard come over...
只有Howard才能解决的 火星探测器...
situation.
的状况
So my friend Leonard
is gonna take you home.
所以我的朋友Leonard会送你回家
- Oh,okay. Let's go, friend Leonard.
- Okay.
- 哦 好吧 咱们走 Leonard朋友
- 好吧
- I'll call ya.
- Yeah.
- 我会给你打电话的
- 好的
So are you a scientist like Howard?
这么说 你和Howard一样是个科学家?
No one's a scientist like Howard.
没有哪个科学家和Howard一样
My mother is so gonna love her.
我老妈肯定会爱死她的
How nice. Maybe they can carpool
when they visit you in federal prison.
真甜蜜阿
也许她们会一起拼车来联邦监狱探视你
I'm sorry. I totally interrupted you.
对不起 我打断你了
What,what, what were you saying?
你刚才说...说些什么?
Just said Howard's a terrific guy.
我就是说 Howard是个棒小伙
He's got a great sense of humor.
他很有幽默感的
He loves his mother... a lot.
也爱他老妈... 爱极了
People say "too much."
大家都觉得"太过了"
I really like that you're
such a loyal friend.
我就喜欢你这种仗义朋友型的
Yeah,I am loyal.
对 我很仗义的
You know,if you look at the big picture.
当然要整体来看
Out of curiosity, did he
ever have a shot with you?
我就好奇问一句 你对他有过感觉吗?
Are you insane? The guy
was wearing an eye patch.
不是吧? 那家伙戴着独眼罩的诶
Then why did you...
那为什么你...
He said that I could
drive a car on Mars.
他说我可以在火星上开车玩
Got it.
了解了
So,can I see you again?
我们会再见面吗?
You're not gonna see me now.
现在你肯定看不见我咯
Cool.
爽哟
Anything?
有反应了吗?
Actually,I was just checking my e-mail.
其实 我是在查我的电邮
But,uh,no,the Rover is not responding.
但 探测器还是没反应
I believe the appropriate metaphor
here involves a river of excrement
此刻最恰当的比喻应该包括
一条臭水沟
and a Native American water vessel
without any means of propulsion.
还有一艘没有推动器的土著船
Hang on. There's got
to be other options.
等等 总归有别的办法吧
You could try calling Triple-A.
也可以试试给独立宇航员联盟打电话
But based on NASA's latest timetable,
they won't get there for 35 years.
不过根据航空航天局最新时间表
他们35年后才能到那儿
Plus I understand you have to be standing next
to the vehicle with your card when they arrive.
而且就算到了 你也得排号
Oh,snap.
牛叉叉的 (snap有"折断一意")
Snap what?
什么断了?
Okay,I guess we have to turn to Plan B.
好吧 那我们得改B计划了
What's Plan B?
B计划是啥?
Erase all the hard drives,
scrap the surveillance tapes,
洗白硬盘 销毁监视录像带
wipe our fingerprints
off every surface and run.
擦干净我们的指纹 开溜
Why wasn't that Plan A?
这咋不是A计划呢?
A NASA spokesman states
that due to the loss of data,
航空航天局发言人称
由于数据丢失
they will most likely be unable to determine
the cause of the Mars Rover's malfunction.
很难确定火星探测器的故障原因
This is not the first time an exploratory
mission to Mars has ended in disappointment.
这已不是火星探险计划第一次
如此失望而终了
Thank God for Plan B.
还好我们有B计划
Howard,didn't you say you
worked on the Mars Rover?
Howard 你不是说过
你在做火星探测器的工作吗?
No,you're mistaken.
没 你记错了
Yeah,when we first met, you said that if I
went out with you, I could drive a car on Mars.
没 我们第一次见面 你就说
如果和你约会 我就可以在火星上开车玩
I don't know what you're talking about.
搞不懂你在说什么
Will you all excuse me?
抱歉离开下
Leonard is subtly signaling that
he'd like to talk to me in private.
Leonard微妙的暗示了
他想和我单独谈谈
No. Yeah,I remember specifically.
不 我很清楚地记得
You started by asking if I was from Mars
because my ass was out of this world.
你一张嘴就问我 是否来自火星
因为我的翘臀地球罕见
Well,that does sound like me, but no.
很有我风格 但不是我啦
- Is there some problem?
- Yeah.
- 出什么状况了吗?
- 是的
Listen,I have to kinda
sneak out for a while.
我得溜出去一会儿
All right,good-bye.
好的 拜拜
No,wait!
不 等下!
If anyone asks you where
I went, you don't know.
要是有人问我去哪儿了 你就说不知道
Whereareyou going?
你要去哪儿?
I can't tell you that.
不能告诉你
Who would ask me?
谁会问我呢?
I can't tell you that,either.
也不能告诉你这个
So you brought me in here to
inform me that you can't tell me
你带我进来就是要告诉我
你不能告诉我
where you're going and you
can't tell me who might ask?
你要去哪儿
也不能告诉我谁会问起?
Yeah,I really didn't think this through.
对呀 是我欠考虑
- Leonard,a moment.
- What?
- Leonard 先别走
- 啥?
If someone-- and of course,we
don't know who this would be--
要是有人... 当然不知到底是谁了...
does ask where you've
gone, what should I say?
问起你去哪儿 我该说什么呢?
I don't know. Just tell
'em I went to the office.
不知道 就说我去办公室了
- Are you going to the office?
- No.
- 你是去办公室吗?
- 不是
Then how can I say it convincingly?
那我怎么能说得自然啊?!
Just say,"Leonard went totheoffice."
就说"Leonard 去了办公室"
All right. Leonard went tothe office.
好吧 Leonard去了办公室
What is... No,not like that!
这是... 不 不是那样的!
Just,"Leonard went to the office."
就说 "Leonard到办公室去了"
This would have worked out a lot better if
you'd just told me you were going to the office.
如果你直接说你要去办公室
就好办多了嘛
I'm going to the office.
我去办公室
See? Why don't I believe you?
看嘛? 凭啥我不信你呢?
I'm going out for a while.
出去一会儿
Okay.
好
Doesn't anyone want to
know where he's going?
没人想知道他去哪儿吗?
Okay,where is he going?
他去哪儿了?
Leonard is going tothe office.
Leonard去办公室了
So how was work today?
今天工作如何?
Busy.
忙死了
I removed an appendix, a gall bladder
and about a foot and a half of bowel.
割了一个阑尾 一个胆囊
还有一段一尺半的肠子
I'm hoping that's three different guys.
不会是一个人的吧
No,just the one.
不 就是一个人
He didn't make it.
他没挺过来
So,how was your day?
你今天过得怎样呢?
Oh,you know,I'm a physicist,so...
I thought about stuff.
你知道 我是个物理学家...
我就思考思考
That's it?
就这些?
Well,I wrote some of it down.
我把一些想法写下来了
Are you done eating?
吃完了吗?
- Uh,yeah.
- Oh,good.
- 完了
- 那好
If I knew you were waiting, I
would've swallowed that lasagna whole.
早知道你等着我
我就把面条一口吞了
You've reached Dr. Stephanie
Barnett. Leave a message.
这是Stephanie Barnett医生家 请留言
Hey,Steph, it's me again,Howard.
嘿Steph 还是我 Howard
Listen,if you're free Friday, maybe we could
have a little something to eat at my place.
如果你周五有空
可以到我那儿吃点东西
My mom cooks a hell of a brisket.
我妈做胸肉可有一手
Let me know. It's Howard.
想好了告诉我哇 我是Howard
I've had her brisket.
Melts in your mouth.
我吃过她做的胸肉 入口即化
Maybe we should think
about going to the bedroom.
不如我们去卧室吧
That's a good idea.
好主意
There's a bed in there, and
I'm very... very,very pro-bed.
里面有床 我可是...可是很喜欢床的
You've reached Dr. Stephanie
Barnett. Leave a message.
这是Stephanie Barnett医生家 请留言
Hey,it's me again.
还是我
Just want to let you know the head
count for dinner Friday has gone up.
想告诉你 下周五的晚餐人数又增加了
My Aunt Betty and Uncle Elliot
are coming in from Palm Springs.
我的Betty婶 Elliot叔要从棕榈泉市过来
Oh,and if anybody should ask, you're
half-Jewish on your mother's side.
要是被问到 你就说你妈那边是犹太人
Okay,call me. It's Howard.
好了 回我电话哟  我是Howard
Don't you think we should
tell him you're not interested?
我们是不是该让他知道
你对他不感冒?
Do you want me to stop and
call him back right now?
你希望现在我停下来 回他电话?
Dear God,no!
上帝呀! 千万表!
Oh,Leonard...
哦 Leonard...
You've reached Dr. Stephanie
Barnett. Leave a message.
这是Stephanie Barnett医生家
请留言
Hey,it's me again. Howard.
嘿 又是我啦 Howard
Listen,my cousins from Fort
Lauderdale are flying in to meet you
我的表兄 要从罗德岱堡飞过来看看你
so that means we're gonna have to
move the dinner to a restaurant.
所以呢 我们得去餐馆吃晚饭了
Tell her we're going
to the Olive Garden!
跟她说 我们去橄榄园吃!
(意式休闲餐厅连锁)
I have a coupon from the paper.
我从报纸上剪了张优惠券!
We're not going to the Olive Garden,Mom!
我们不去橄榄园 老妈!
Oh,Mr. Bigshot with his Red Lobster.
大人物和他的红龙虾哟
I'll call you back when
we firm up the details.
确认了细节以后我再打给你
It's Howard.
我是Howard哟
- New shirts?
- Yeah,a couple.
- 新衬衣吗?
- 对 刚买几件
- Nice.
- Thank you.
- 不错嘛
- 谢谢
So,who's the girl?
那妞儿是谁?
I'm sorry?
你说什么?
Well,last time you bought a new
shirt was when we were dating.
上回你买新衬衫 就是咱俩约会的时候
So what we did was in fact dating?
这么说 咱俩那真算约会了?
Well,yeah,we did have a date.
是啊 我们是约了一次
Exactly. Thank you.
正是 谢谢
Do me a favor. Tell Koothrappali
that next time you see him.
帮我个忙吧 下回看到Koothrappali
告诉他(咱俩约过一回)
So,who is she?
我说 她是谁哦?
Oh,she's a doctor.
哦 是个医生
Oh,nice.
哟 不错嘛
A doctor doctor, or
a you kind of doctor?
是正牌医生呢 还是你这样的博士?
Doctor doctor. Surgical
resident. Smart,pretty.
人家就是医生 外科住院医生
又聪明 又漂亮
Let me ask you something.
我来问问你
If your friend thinks he's dating
someone, but he's not because,in fact,
如果你的朋友觉得 自己在和一妞儿约会
可其实不是
you're dating her, does
that make you a bad person?
因为你在和她约会
你这样是不是不厚道啊?
- Well,that depends.
- On what?
- 这也得看情况
- 看啥情况?
Is that friend Wolowitz?
那朋友是不是Wolowitz?
- Yeah.
- Screw him. You're fine.
- 对
- 去死吧他 你没做错
Are you sure?
真的吗?
Well,have you slept with her yet?
跟她上床了没有?
You dog!
小子你行啊!
Good for you.
挺好的
- Does that change things?
- No.
- 上床了有啥不一样咩?
- 没有
So why'd you ask?
那你干嘛要问?
I'm nosy. See ya.
我八卦呗 回见
Howard,get the door!
Howard 快开门!
Really? Is that what
you dohen someone knocks?
真的? 有人敲门你就这德行吗?
Thank you. I had no idea!
多谢你啊! 我总算知道了!
Hey,buddy. What brings you
to my little slice of hell?
嘿 兄弟 什么风把你吹到
我的地狱小屋来了?
Who is it?
是谁啊?
It's Leonard!
是Leonard!
You're gonna have to play outside!
要玩别进屋玩啊!
I'm not dressed to receive!
我衣冠不整没法见人!
No one cares,Ma! So,what's up?
没人要见你 老妈! 怎么了?
Listen,I need to talk
to you about something.
有件事我得跟你谈谈
Momentito. Yello.
等一下下噻 里好~
Oh,Stephanie, thanks for
calling me back. I was worried...
喔 Stephanie 谢谢你回我电话
我正担心...
No,I understand. Sure,we
can be friends. Absolutely.
没事 我理解啦 我们还是朋友
当然啦
Thanks for calling.
谢谢你打电话来
Yeah,you have a nice day,too.
嗯 也祝你今天愉快
You are dead to me.
你死定了
Okay,who gets the extra dumpling?
多余的这份饺子谁吃?
Rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock.
石头-剪子-布-蜥蜴-史波克
Okay,one of us is going to
have to stop putting up Spock.
我说 得有一个人
不能再出史波克了啊
*******
怎么决定是谁呢
Rock-paper-scissors-
lizard-Spock.
石头-剪子-布-蜥蜴-史波克
- Oh,hey,guys.
- Hello.
- 大家好
- 好啊
Hi,Howard.
嗨 Howard
- Howard?
- Sheldon.
- Sheldon
Howard is employing a schoolyard
paradigm in which you are,
Howard决定使用操场模型
在这个模型里
for all intents and purposes,deceased.
无论从哪一点看 你都是死的
He intends to act on this
by not speaking to you,
他希望恪守这一规范
所以不和你说话
feigning an inability to
hear you when you speak
你说话的时候 也假装听不见
and otherwise refusing to
acknowledge your existence.
不然就拒绝承认你的存在
That's just ridiculous.
这也太可笑了
Why are you cooperating with him?
你怎么成他同伙了?
I don't make the rules, Leonard.
规矩不是我定的 Leonard
Howard,come on. I didn't plan on
this. These things just happen.
Howard 得了吧 我又不是故意的
事情就是发生了嘛
Usually not to me, but they do happen.
一般呢 我撞不上
不过这种事情还是会有
Did someone just feel a cold breeze?
你们有没有感到一阵阴风?
I believe this is an extension
of the death metaphor.
这也算是"死亡隐喻"的延伸含义吧
The cold breeze is the so-called ectoplasmic
issue of a disembodied soul passing by.
阴风就是灵魂的躯壳飘过的结果
所谓的空灵物
You know,screw it. I'm
just gonna eat the dumpling.
表废话 饺子你们不吃我吃了
Oh,hi,Steph. Come on in.
嗨 Steph 快进来
Is this a bad time?
我来的不时候?
Yeah,but I don't see a better
one on the horizon,so...
对 不过眼下也瞅不见更好的时候
Oh,if it isn't Mrs. Dead to Me.
哦 这不是"死定了"夫人嘛
- Hello,Howard.
- Sheldon?
- 你好 Howard
I'm sorry,you violated the terms of your
metaphor by acknowledging her existence.
对不起 你违背了自己的隐喻条款
承认了她的存在
I'm out.
我不玩了
He just won't listen to me.
他就是不听我说
Okay,I guess it'll just
be the three of us then.
好 那估计就我们三个玩了吧
- Lisa's gonna be disappointed.
- Yeah.
- Lisa一定失望死了
- 没错
Lisa?
Yeah,my roommate. She just went
through a really bad breakup
对啊 我室友 刚分手 伤心得要死
and I thought she might like
to meet somebody fun like you.
我想 要是她碰上个有意思的人
比如你 肯定很开心
Leonard,Stephanie, you're
alive! It's a miracle!
Leonard Stephanie 你们活过来了!
神啊 奇迹出现了!
So,anyway,Lisa, I just wanted to tell you
again how much I enjoyed the other night,
Lisa 我就是告诉你
那天晚上我很开心
and again, I'm sorry for how it ended.
再次抱歉啦 结局不怎么好
But again,if you could
let me know about Friday.
不过希望你尽快告诉我 周五是否可以来
My mother needs a head count so she
can know how big a brisket to get.
我妈急着数人头呢
好知道得做多大的胸肉
Howard,Howard, look at this.
Howard Howard 瞧瞧这个!
- Anyway,call me.It's Howard.
- The possibility of life on Mars has long fascinated scientists and laypersons alike.
- 打给我哦 我是Howard
- 长久以来 关于火星上有无生命的猜想
It's unclear how the Mars Rover got into
the crevice, but one thing's certain:
目前还不知道 火星探测器是怎么
进入了裂隙 但有一点可以肯定
The data which it has sent back
contain the first clear indications
它发回的数据中 第一次清楚显示
that there may have been life on Mars.
火星上曾可能有过生命迹象
It's a scientific discovery that has
staggering implications for all mankind.
这一科学发现 对全人类来说
都是惊人的成就
Unfortunately,we'll never
know who's responsible.
可惜的是 再也无法得知
这一切的始作俑者究竟是谁
Son of a bitch.
他奶奶的
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
--------------------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------------------
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 八重樱 王泳东 opp
校对: 欧屁屁
时间轴: 咔肉肉